Guide to the Helen and Kurt Wolff Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1905-1992; Series V; 3.13' (8 boxes)
  - WRITINGS OF OTHERS
    - Cibulka, Hans
      See: Correspondence, The Christian Science Monitor, Box 4, folder 148
    - Cruttwell, Patrick
      - "Fiction Chronicle," article, offprint, The Hudson Review, 1965 Oct (Box 74, Folder 2081)
    - Davis, Liselotte M.
      "Interview with Helen Wolff," article, [typescript photocopy?]
      See: Correspondence, Box 4, folder 187
    - De Bosis, Lauro
      - "The Story of my Death," autobiographical statement, reprint, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 2082)
    - Dessoir, Max
      - Vom Jenseits der Seele, excerpt, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2083)
    - Du Bos, Charles
      - ["Come Valery demandait..."], journal fragment, transcription, typescript carbon, 1922 Jun 10 (Box 74, Folder 2084)
    - Eco, Umberto
      - "Leçon Inaugurale," lecture, printed version, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 2085)
    - Farokhzad, Freydoun
      - Poem, holograph copy in hand of Kurt Wolff, n.y. Apr 20 (Box 74, Folder 2086)
    - Fuchs, Albert
      - "Broch: Der Tod des Vergil ," article, offprint, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2087)
      - "Zur Sprachbehandlung in Hermann Brochs Tod des Vergil ," article, offprint, Bulletin de la Faculté des Lettres de Strasbourg, 1963 Apr (Box 74, Folder 2088)
    - Galantière, Lewis
      - "A Few Words About Translation," lecture, typescript photocopy, 1962 Dec 6 (Box 74, Folder 2089)
    - Gebsattel, Victor Emil, Freiherr von
      - "Die Wiederkehr von Lou Andreas- Salomé," poem, drafts, holograph and typescript carbon, corrected, 1963 Jan (Box 74, Folder 2090)
    - Gelley, Alexander
      - "Art and Reality in Die Blechtrommel ," article, reprint, Forum for Modern Lnaguage Studies, 1967 Jan (Box 74, Folder 2091)
    - George, Stefan Anton
      - "Einverleibung," poem, holograph copy in unidentified hand (Box 74, Folder 2092)
    - Göbel, Wolfram
      - "Der Ernst Rowohlt Verlag 1910-1913," article, printed version, Börsenblatt für den Deutschen Buchhandel, 1974 Apr 9 (Box 74, Folder 2093)
      - "Der Ernst Rowohlt Verlag 1910-1913," article, offprint, Archiv für Geschichte des Buchwesens, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2094)
    - Goldstein, R. L.
      - "Forensic Pyschiatry and Literature Part I," article, printed version, The Psychiatric Journal of the University of Ottawa, photocopy, 1986 Mar (Box 74, Folder 2095)
    - Gombrich, E. H. (Ernst Hans)
      - [Empty folder] (Box 74, Folder 2096)
      - "Das Spiel mit den Dominosteinen," article, printed version, Literatur und Kunst, 1983 Jun 25
    - Grambow, Jürgen
      - "Heimat im Vergangenen," article, printed version, Sinn und Form, photocopy, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 2097)
    - Grass, Günter
      - "An die Abgeordneten des Deutschen Bundestages," speech, printed version, photocopy, 1983 Nov (Box 74, Folder 2098)
      - "Chodowieki zum Beispiel," article, printed version, Die Zeit, 1991 Jun 14
      - "Im Hinterhof: Bericht über eine Reise nach Nicaragua," article, printed version, Die Zeit, 1982 Oct 1
      - "On Loss," speech, printout, 1992 Nov 18 (Box 74, Folder 2099)
    - Greve, Ludwig
      - "Hannah Arendt," poem, printed version, Neue Deutsche Hefte, 1977 Jan 24 (Box 74, Folder 2100)
    - Grothe, Wolfgang
      - "Die Neue Rundschau des Verlages S. Fischer," article, printed version, Börsenblatt für den Deutschen Buchhandel, 1961 Dec 14 (Box 74, Folder 2101)
    - Gundolf, Friedrich
      - "Geschichte der Philosophie," poem, drafts (copies?), typescript carbon, corrected, 1912, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2102)
      - "Die Ruhigen," poem, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2103)
      - "Weltgeschichte," poem, copy, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2104)
      - Untitled poems, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2105)
    - Guthke, Karl [Siegfried?]
      - "Franz Werfel Anfänge..." article, offprint, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2106)
    - Harari, Manya
      - ["Within the space of ten days..." draft, article, thermofax of typescript, corrected, 1958 Nov (Box 75, Folder 2107)
    - Harms, Ernest
      - "Carl Gustav Jung: Defender of Freud and the Jews," article, reprint, The Psychiatric Quarterly, 1946 Apr (Box 75, Folder 2108)
    - Haydn, Hiram
      - "Melville Cane," article, printed version, The American Scholar, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2109)
    - Heidegger, Martin
      - ["Der Spruch des Heraklit..."], transcribed excerpt, "Brief über den "Humanismus"," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2110)
      - ["Der Spruch sagt..."], transcribed excerpt, Holzwege, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2111)
    - Heise, Carl George
      - "Werner Haftmann," article, printed version, Die Zeit, 1962 Mar 23 (Box 75, Folder 2112)
    - Herburger, Günter
      - "Training," poem, printed version, Neue Rundschau, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 2113)
    - Hertog, Susan
      - ["I spent the long summer days..."], autobiographical statement, printout, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2114)
    - Hesse, Ninon
      - "Das Erdküglein," article, printed version, Neue Zürcher Zeitung, 1960 Apr 3
    - Howe, Irving
      - "The West Bank Trap," article, printed version, The New Republic, photocopy, 1983 Jul 4 (Box 75, Folder 2115)
    - Howes, Barbara
      - "A Point of View," poem, printed version, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2116)
    - Hrushovski, Benjamin
      - Translation of "In the Middle of this Century," poem, printout, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2117)
    - Ivask, Ivar
      - Snow Lessons, poems, printed version, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 2118)
    - [Jaanus?], Maire
      - "Some Letters of Hermann Broch to Edith," article, printed version, Books Abroad, photocopy, 1974 Aug (Box 75, Folder 2119)
    - Jacobi, Jolande Székacs
      - ["C. G. Jung wurde im Jahre..."], article, typescript carbon, 1949 Aug (Box 75, Folder 2120)
      - "Freud und Jung," article, printed version, Literatur und Kunst, 1956 May 6
      - "Die Mutter," article, offprint, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 2121)
      - "Prof. Carl Gustav Jung," article, offprint, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 2122)
    - Johnson, Uwe
      - ["I had no political..."], open letter, printed version, Atlas, 1962 Feb (Box 75, Folder 2123)
    - Jung, C. G. (Carl Gustav)
      - "Sigmund Freud," article, printed version, photocopy, 1939 Oct 1
      - "Zur Umerziehung des deutschen Volkes," article, printed version, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2123a)
    - Keel, John S.
      - "Sir Herbert Read on Teaching Methods," article, printout, 1984 May 23 (Box 75, Folder 2124)
    - Lasker-Schüler, Else
      - "Ich räume auf!" article, printed version, 1925 (Box 75, Folder 2125)
      - "Paul Zech," poem, [transcribed copy?], typescript and typescript carbon (Box 75, Folder 2126)
    - Levitsky, Serge
      - "Rose Koffmann-Pasternak: La Mère du poète," article, printed version, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2127)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow
      - "Caprice," poem, [printed version?], The Smith College Monthly, 1926 Oct (Box 75, Folder 2128)
      - ["I recently spent a month..."], article, printed version, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2129)
      - "Thoughts on Old Age," article, printed version, Smith Alumnae Quarterly, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 2130)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles Augustus)
      - "Is Civilization Press," article, offprint, Reader's Digest, 1964 Jul (Box 75, Folder 2131)
    - Lister, R. P. [(Richard Percival)?]
      - "The Australian Sack Knot," article, printed version, 1960 Feb 20 (Box 75, Folder 2132)
    - Manheim, Ralph
      - "In the Translator's Kitchen," article, printed version, The Times Literary Supplement, photocopy, 1970 Sep 18 (Box 75, Folder 2133)
    - Merton, Thomas
      - Peace in the Post Christian Era, typescript photocopy, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2134)
      - "The Pasternak Affair," article, thermal fax copy of typescript, 1958 Dec 5 (Box 75, Folder 2135)
    - Migone, Bartolomeo
      - "Nicaragua: Come Lavora la Contra," article, printed version, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2136)
      - "Nicarague, ad Achuapa tra Sandinisti e Fucilate Contras..." article, printed version, La Domenica, 1986 Aug 22
    - Mitgang, Herbert
      - "Jay Gatsby Meets the Russians," article, printed version, The Nation, photocopy, 1986 Aug 2 (Box 75, Folder 2137)
      - "Profiles," article, printed version, The New Yorker, photocopy, 1982 Aug 2 (Box 75, Folder 2138)
    - Origo, Iris
      - [April 16th. Sailed from Siracusa..."] diary, typescript, corrected, photocopy, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2139)
      - "Biography, True and False," article, printed version, The Atlantic, 1959 Feb (Box 75, Folder 2140)
      - "The Hospital of the Holy Spirit," printed version, photocopy, 1959 Apr (Box 75, Folder 2141)
      - "The Tuscan and His Land," drafts, outline and prologue, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected, 1960, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2142)
      - "The Valley and the Mountain," drafts, outline and first chapter, typescript and typrscript carbon, corrected (Box 75, Folder 2143)
    - Otten, Karl
      - "Herbst 1939," poem, holograph facsimile and printed version (Box 75, Folder 2144)
      - "Ravenna," poem, printed version, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 2145)
      - "Die Stille," poem, printed version, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2146)
    - Oz, Amos
      - "'Al-Fajr'--Hope for a New Day," article, printed version, The Nation, photocopy, 1983 Nov 5 (Box 75, Folder 2147)
      - "Has Israel Altered its Vision?" article, printed version, New York Times Magazine, 1982 Jul 11
      - "The Imagination of the State and the Imagination of the Writer," article, printout photocopy (Box 75, Folder 2148)
      - "The Meaning of Homeland: The Tragic Confrontaion of Two Rights," lecture, typescript, corrected, 1974 Nov (Box 75, Folder 2149)
      - "Peace and Love and Compromise," speech, printout, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 2150)
      - "The Savage and the Well," novel (incomplete), printout photocopy, [1988?] Jul 19 (Box 75, Folder 2151)
    - Perera, Ronald
      - "Three Poems of Günter Grass," interview, printed version, Smith Alumnae Quarterly, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 2152)
    - Pfeiffer, Ernst
      - "Die Historie von der Lou oder..." article, typescript carbon, corrected (Box 75, Folder 2153)
      - "Lou Andreas-Salomé," article, offprint, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 2154)
      - Poems, typescript carbon, 1972, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2155)
      - "Über ein Sonett von Rilke," article, offprint, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 2156)
    - Pieper, Josef
      - "On Clarity," speech, printed version, Chronicles, 1988 Apr (Box 75, Folder 2157)
      - "On the Language of the Mirandum," article, printed version, Temenos, photocopy, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 2158)
    - Plyushch, Leonid
      - ["From child development studies..."], typescript photocopy, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2159)
    - Porat, Zephyra
      - "The Living Dog and the Dead Lion..." article, offprint, The Jerusalem Quarterly, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2160)
    - Raabe, Paul
      - "Morgenrot!--Die Tage Dämmern!," article, printed version, Der Monat, 1964 Aug (Box 76, Folder 2161)
    - Raddatz, Fritz J.
      - "Tradition und Kommerz," article, printed version, 1966 Sep (Box 76, Folder 2162)
    - Read, Herbert [Edward]
      - "Zum 85. Geburtstag von Profesor Dr. Carl Gustav Jung," essay, printed version, 1960 Jul 26 (Box 76, Folder 2163)
    - Rietzschel, Thomas
      - "Literat oder Büchermacher? Ein Doppelporträt der Verleger Kurt Wolff und Ernst Rowohlt," article, typescript photocopy (Box 76, Folder 2164)
    - Rivers, Larry
      - "Dear Teen-age Audience," article, printed version, n.d.
    - Rovit, Earl
      - "Jewish Humor and American Life," article, printed version, The American Scholar, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 2165)
    - Salzmann, Karl H.
      - "Kurt Wolff, der Verleger," article, printed version, Börsenblatt für den Deutschen Buchhandel, 1958 Dec 22 (Box 76, Folder 2166)
      - "Kurt Wolff, der Verleger," article, offprint, Sonderdruck (Box 76, Folder 2167)
    - Sanders, Ivan
      - "Simple Elements and Violent Combinations..." article, reprint, Judaism: A Quarterly Journal of Jewish Life and Thought, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2168)
    - Saroyan, William
      - "What's Going on Around Here?" article, printed version (Box 76, Folder 2169)
    - Scheffler, Heinrich
      - "Vom Geschäft, Bücher zu Verlegen, oder ein Beruf für Gentlemen?" article, printed version, photocopy, [1983?] (Box 76, Folder 2170)
    - Schmeichel-Falkenberg, Beate
      - "Kurt Tucholsky's Letzte Jahre in Schweden 1929-1935," article, printed version, photocopy, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 2171)
    - Schumacher, Martin von
      - "Miszelle: Autoren und Verleger in der Deutschen Inflationszeit," article, printed version, Vierteljahrschrift für Wirtschaftsgeschichte, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2172)
    - Selander, Sten
      - "Ein Deutscher Proust," review, typescript carbon, corrected, 1931 Jun 28 (Box 76, Folder 2173)
    - Simpson, Jerry H.
      - "Air Travel," story, printout, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2174)
    - Skwara, Erlich Wolfgang
      - "Hermann Brochs Grab," article, printed version, Literatur und Kritik, photocopy, 1975 Feb (Box 76, Folder 2175)
    - Smith, Desmond
      - "A Conversation with Günter Grass," article, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2176)
    - Stehle, Hansjacob
      - "Communism: Nobody Can Give a Completely Accurate Definition," article, typescript, photocopy, 1967 Mar 31 (Box 76, Folder 2177)
    - Sullivan, Frank
      - "The Forgotten Bach," article, printed version, The New Yorker, 1950 Nov 4 (Box 76, Folder 2178)
    - [Torberg, Freidrich?]
      - "Zu einem Ungedruckten Gedicht von Else Lasker-Schüler," article, printed version, Forvm, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 2179)
    - Viertel, [Berthold?]
      - "Einsam," poem, typescript, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2180)
    - Vietta, Egon
      - "Hermann Broch," article, typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2181)
      - "Hermann Broch und seine Schlafwandler ," article, typescript carbon, corrected, 1947 Oct 28 (Box 76, Folder 2182)
    - Wagenbach, Klaus
      - "Marginalien," radio broadcast, typescript carbon, 1963 Oct 29 (Box 76, Folder 2183)
    - Werfel, Franz
      - "Der Dirigent," poem, holograph copy [in Kurt Wolff's hand?] (Box 76, Folder 2184)
    - Whalen, Tom
      - "Sestina for Italo Calvino," poem, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2185)
    - Wilson, Edmund
      - "Notes on Doctor Zhivago ," essay, typescript (Box 76, Folder 2186)
    - [Wolff, Elizabeth?]
      - "Plan zur Begründung eines Verlagshauses für Literatur, Geist und Kunst in Darmstadt," article, typescript carbon, corrected (Box 76, Folder 2187)
    - Wood, Douglas
      - "An Interview with Donald Harington," article, printed version, The Undermountain Review, photocopy, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 2188)
    - Zeller, Bernhard
      - "Erinnerung an den Schriftsteller Karl Otten 1889 - 1989," article, [printout?] photocopy, 1989 Oct 18 (Box 76, Folder 2189)
      - "Ludwig Greve zum Gedächtnis," article, offprint, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 2190)
    - Ziegfeld, Richard E.
      - "Exile Author/Exile Publisher: Uwe Johnson and Helen Wolff," article, printout (Box 76, Folder 2191)
    - Unidentified
      - Poems, 1963-78, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2192)
      - Other writings, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 2193)
- Subject Files, 1932-1994; Series VI; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  Series VI, Subject Files, is organized into two subseries: Individuals and Organizations and Topics.
  - INDIVIDUALS AND ORGANIZATIONS
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1960-61 (Box 77, Folder 2194)
    - Allilueva, Svetlana, 1967 Aug 3 (Box 77, Folder 2195)
    - American Center of P.E.N., 1984-89, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2196)
    - Andreas-Salomé, Lou, 1964 Oct 3 (Box 77, Folder 2197)
    - Arendt, Hannah, 1960-93, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2198)
    - Bahr, Hermann, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2199)
    - Barloewen, Constantin von, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2200)
    - Barthelme, Donald, [1989] (Box 77, Folder 2201)
    - [Beltrami, L. (Luca)?], 1962 Jun 4 (Box 77, Folder 2202)
    - Ben Jelloun, Tahar, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2203)
    - Bender, Hans, 1954 Aug 20 (Box 77, Folder 2204)
    - Benjamin, Walter, 1985 Jun 15
    - Bioy Casares, Adolpho, 1990 Feb 5 (Box 77, Folder 2205)
    - Böll, Heinrich, 1959 Oct 30 (Box 77, Folder 2206)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2207)
    - Brand, C. P. (Charles Peter), 1958 Jan 3
    - Bremond, Henri, 1962 Nov 18 (Box 77, Folder 2208)
    - Broch, Hermann, 1932-63, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2209)
    - Brod, Max, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 2210)
    - Bryher, [1983?] (Box 77, Folder 2211)
    - Calvino, Italo, 1957-88, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2212)
    - Cane, Melville, 1976-78 (Box 77, Folder 2213)
    - Carossa, Hans, 1947-51 (Box 77, Folder 2214)
    - Chagall, Marc, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2215)
    - Cocteau, Jean, 1984 May 13
    - Croce, Benedetto, 1962, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2216)
    - Curtius, Ernst Robert, 1956 Apr 20 (Box 77, Folder 2217)
    - Delacorte Gallery, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2218)
    - Demetz, Peter, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2219)
    - Djilas, Milovan, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 2220)
    - Duggan, Alfred Leo, 1960, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2221)
    - Durrell, Lawrence, n.d.
    - Du Sautoy, Peter, 1973 Oct 12 (Box 77, Folder 2222)
    - Eco, Umberto, 1984-91, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2223)
    - Editorial Seix Barral, 1962 Jan 5 (Box 77, Folder 2224)
    - Edschmid, Kasimir, 1960 Oct (Box 77, Folder 2225)
    - Ehrenstein, Albert, 1958 Apr 2 (Box 77, Folder 2226)
    - Einstein, Carl, 1963 Jan 14 (Box 77, Folder 2227)
    - Ellerman, J. R. (John Reeves), 1961 Dec 8 (Box 77, Folder 2228)
    - Enzenberger, Hans Magnus, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 2229)
    - Eranos Conference, 1950-58, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2230)
    - Erenburg, Ilia, 1960 Aug 22 (Box 77, Folder 2231)
    - Faber du Faur, Emma, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2232)
    - Die Fackel, 1916-23 (Box 77, Folder 2233)
    - Faux, Claude, 1959, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 2234)
    - Feltrinelli editore, 1959-72, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2235)
    - [Fénelon, François de Salignac de La Mothe?], n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2236)
    - Feraoun, Mouloud, 1962 Mar (Box 77, Folder 2237)
    - Frisch, Max, 1983-92, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2238)
    - Fröhlich, Hans J. (Hans Jürgen), n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2239)
    - Furtwängler, Wilhelm, 1962 Dec (Box 77, Folder 2240)
    - Gallimard (Firm), 1990-91 (Box 77, Folder 2241)
    - George, Stefan Anton, 1952 Feb 1 (Box 77, Folder 2242)
    - Ginzburg, Evgeniia Semenovna, 1981, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 2243)
    - Graetz, Wolfgang, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2244)
    - Grass, Günter, 1961-94, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2245-2247)
    - Greve, Ludwig, 1991 Jul 15 (Box 77, Folder 2248)
    - Grzimek, Bernard; Grzimek, Michael, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2249)
    - Gundolf, Friedrich, 1962-63
    - Haas, Willy, 1961, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 2250)
    - Handke, Peter, 1977 Jul 31
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1978-94, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2251-2253)
    - Hardt, Kurd de, 1958 Nov 29
    - Harington, Donald, 1965-87, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2254)
    - Hasenclever, Walter, 1957-63, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2255)
    - Hassan, Sana, 1987 Jan 25 (Box 78, Folder 2256)
    - Haywood, Max, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 2257)
    - Heise, Carl George, 1961, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 2258)
    - Heissenbüttel, Helmut, 1963 May (Box 78, Folder 2259)
    - Herburger, Günter, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2260)
    - Heym, Georg, 1960 Oct 28 (Box 78, Folder 2261)
    - Hibbert, Christopher, 1962 Sep (Box 78, Folder 2262)
    - Hildegard, Saint, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2263)
    - Höllerer, Walter, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 2264)
    - Homet, Marcel, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2265)
    - Inter Nationes, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2266)
    - Johnson, Uwe, 1961-84, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2267)
    - Jouhandeau, Marcel, 1959 Sep 15 (Box 78, Folder 2268)
    - Jovanovich, William, 1966-72, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2269)
    - Jung, C. G. (Carl Gustav), 1934-61, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2270-2271)
    - JWB (Organization). Jewish Book Council, 1977 Dec 12 (Box 78, Folder 2272)
    - Kafka, Franz, 1982 Jun 10 (Box 78, Folder 2273)
    - Kahnweiler, M. D. H., n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2274)
    - Kiaulehn, Walther, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2275)
    - Kassner, Rudolf, 1946 Feb 1 (Box 78, Folder 2276)
    - Killy, Walther, 1962 Jan 15 (Box 78, Folder 2277)
    - Kilvert, Robert Francis, 1960 Nov 6 (Box 78, Folder 2278)
    - Klee, Felix; Klee, Paul, 1961, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2279)
    - Kleine, Gisela, 1984 Feb 11 (Box 78, Folder 2280)
    - Kleist, Heinrich von, 1961 Nov 19
    - Kolb, Annette, 1965 Feb 2
    - Konrád, György, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 2281)
    - Krätzer, Anita, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2282)
    - Landshoff, Fritz Helmut, 1985 Jan 18 (Box 78, Folder 2283)
    - Lange, Monique, 1962 Jun 17 (Box 78, Folder 2284)
    - Laughlin, James, 1950 Jan 16 (Box 78, Folder 2285)
    - Lem, Stanislaw, 1985-86 (Box 78, Folder 2286)
    - Leuschner, Bruno, 1910-1965 (Box 78, Folder 2287)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow, 1956-94 (Box 78, Folder 2288)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spender, 1993 Dec (Box 78, Folder 2289)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles Augustus), 1960-90 (Box 78, Folder 2290)
    - Lorenz, Konrad, 1965-89, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2291)
    - Mahler, Alma, 1960, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2292)
    - Manheim, Ralph, 1974-92 (Box 78, Folder 2293)
    - Mann, Heinrich, 1972 Jan 27 (Box 78, Folder 2294)
    - Mann, Thomas, 1961 Dec 17
    - Matthias, Lisa, 1962 May 4
    - McCarthy, Mary, 1960 Jan 21 (Box 78, Folder 2295)
    - Mellon, Paul, n.d.
    - Meyer, Georg Heinrich, 1959 Nov 17 (Box 78, Folder 2296)
    - Mitgutsch, Anna, 1985, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2297)
    - Moerath, Inge; Miller, Arthur, 1967 Jun 1 (Box 78, Folder 2298)
    - Monarch Book Company, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2299)
    - Montebello, Philippe de, 1985 Nov 3
    - Morris, Jan, 1961-82, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2300)
    - Mühr, Alfred, 1958, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2301)
    - Neumann, Robert, 1962
    - Niedermayer, Max, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 2302)
    - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1964 Nov 13 (Box 78, Folder 2303)
    - Origo, Iris, 1982-84, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2304)
    - Otten, Karl, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2305)
    - Oz, Amos, 1972-92, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2306-2308)
    - Ozick, Cynthia, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2309)
    - Panofsky, Wolfgang Kurt Hermann, 1961 Jul 21 (Box 78, Folder 2310)
    - Pantheon Books, 1944-90, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2311)
    - Pascal, Blaise, 1962 Oct 14 (Box 78, Folder 2312)
    - Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich, 1958-90, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2313)
    - Paulding, Gouverneur, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2314)
    - P.E.N. Congress, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 2315)
    - Pieper, Josef, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2316)
    - Pinder, Wilhelm, 1962 May 7 (Box 79, Folder 2317)
    - Preetorius, Emil, 1963 Jun 21 (Box 79, Folder 2318)
    - Random House (Firm), 1959-61 (Box 79, Folder 2319)
    - Rangel, Carlos, 1988 Jan 28 (Box 79, Folder 2320)
    - Rawicz, Piotr, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2321)
    - [Reimann?], Max, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2322)
    - Reinhold, Peter, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2323)
    - Remarque, Erich Maria, 1962 Dec 1
    - Rilke, Rainer Maria, 1962 Oct 23 (Box 79, Folder 2324)
    - Röthlisberger, Marcel, 1963 May 31
    - Rougemont, Denis de, 1960-61
    - Rowohlt (Firm), 1959-60 (Box 79, Folder 2325)
    - Runciman, Steven, 1965 Jul 8
    - S. Fischer Verlag, 1959, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 2326)
    - Saiko, George, 1986 Feb 7
    - Saint-Phalle, Thérèse de, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2327)
    - Salinger, J. D. (Jerome David), 1961-62 (Box 79, Folder 2328)
    - Salter, Stefan, 1985 Feb 8 (Box 79, Folder 2329)
    - Sauerländer, Wolfgang, 1977 Nov 14 (Box 79, Folder 2330)
    - Schabert, Kyrill, 1959-62, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2331)
    - Schickele, René, 1961 Dec 1 (Box 79, Folder 2331a)
    - Schiffrin, André (Box 79, Folder 2332)
    - Schiller-Nationalmuseum, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2333)
    - Schmidt, Arno, 1958-91 (Box 79, Folder 2334)
    - Schocken, Salman, 1959, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2335)
    - Scholz, Wilhelm von, b. 1874, 1950 Jul 15